RG 079:005, Department of Environmental Protection: Air, Waste and Water
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Bureau of Water Management, 1920-1979
  - Permitting, Enforcement, and Remediation Division, 1928-1979; bulk 1969-1977
    - Correspondence Files, 1997-050
      - East Lyme (Box 25)
        - Helen Stratos House (Box 25)
        - East Lyme Tennis Club (Box 25)
        - Rocky Neck (Box 25)
        - William H. Wilson (Box 25)
        - Wand-a-Magic Self Service Car Wash (Box 25)
      - Easton (Box 25)
        - Easton Misc (Box 25)
        - Delaware Estates (Box 25)
        - The Snows Dairy Co. Of Boston (Box 25)
        - Easton Refuse Area, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - Easton Refuse Area/Town of Easton Hearing, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - Easton Study of Land Disposal Sites (Box 25)
        - Abatement-Municipal Refuse Disposal Area (Box 25)
      - East Windsor (Box 26)
        - East Windsor Misc., 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Kement Landfill (Box 26)
        - Castle & Cook Mushroom Co. (Box 26)
        - Cumberland Farms (Box 26)
        - ESPE (Box 26)
        - Ketch Brook Watershed (Box 26)
        - Northern Capitol Region Disposal Facility Hearing, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Botticello Norcap (Box 26)
        - LCK Corp, 3 folders (Box 26)
        - Philip Grant (Box 26)
        - Town of East Windsor (Box 26)
        - U.S Dept. of Army (Box 26)
        - John & Elizabeth Balch (Box 26)
        - Austin Company, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - All American Products, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Bowers Printing Ink (Box 26)
        - Broad Brook Moratorium (Box 26)
        - Mascaro’s Auto Radiator Service (Box 26)
        - Mallinckrodt, Inc. (Box 26)
        - Mill Pond Village (Box 26)
        - PPG Industries (Box 26)
        - Park Plaza Trailer Park, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - United Auto Sales or East Windsor (Box 26)
        - Skip’s Septic Service (Box 26)
        - George Snyder/School Hill Well (Box 26)
        - Target Industries (Box 26)
        - Rivergate Apartments (Box 26)
        - Southern Auto Sales (Box 26)
        - Richard Weller Potato Shipping (Box 26)
        - Hunt Well Field Water Treatment Plan (Box 26)
      - Ellington (Box 27)
        - Ellington Misc. (Box 27)
        - Crystal Lake Sanitary Survey (Box 27)
        - Acromold Products Corp. (Box 27)
        - Drazen Structures, Inc., Including Hearing (Box 27)
        - Ed Bolles Ent. (Box 27)
        - Ellington Estates (Box 27)
        - Ellington Lots (Box 27)
        - Ellington Habitat (Box 27)
        - Hathaway Road Subdivision (Box 27)
        - Heatherstone Ridge Subdivision (Box 27)
        - K & R Printers (Box 27)
        - Liebman Apt./Nitrate Problem (Box 27)
        - Lith-Kem-Ko (Box 27)
        - Lughenbuhl Site/Rte 83 (Box 27)
        - Moser Dairy Farms, 2 folders (Box 27)
        - William Klee (Box 27)
        - Mike’s Repair Service (Box 27)
        - Nieman Bros. Farm (Box 27)
        - Paul Panebranco - Hearing (Box 27)
        - Rockville Water & Aqueduct, 2 folders (Box 27)
        - Townhouse/Dave Webster, 1776 (Box 27)
      - Enfield (Box 28)
        - Enfield Misc., 4 folders (Box 28)
        - Town of Enfield - Hearing (Box 28)
        - Bethel Comasec, Inc. (Box 28)
        - Bigelow Sanford Carpet Co. (Box 28)
        - S. Camerota & Sons (Box 28)
        - CT State Prison, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Dairy Mart, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Dary Mart - Hearing (Box 28)
        - DeBell & Richardson, Inc. (Box 28)
        - Fiore Oldsmobile (Box 28)
        - First Healthcare Corp. (Box 28)
        - Gale Motors, Inc. (Box 28)
        - Gayle Toyota (Box 28)
        - Goodyear Tire & Rubber Co. (Box 28)
        - Goodyear Service Store (Box 28)
        - Hallmark Cards, Inc. - Hearing (Box 28)
        - Enfield Leachate Treatment System/EPA Grant, 4 folders (Box 28)
        - Leybold - Heraeus Vacuum System, Inc. (Box 28)
        - May Stores Shopping Center (Box 28)
        - Magic Minit Car Wash (Box 28)
        - Magnini & McCormick (Box 28)
        - Mac, Inc., Maaco Autobody (Box 28)
        - Meadowfield Auto Body (Box 28)
        - Shannon-Kilkenny, Inc. D/b/a Midas Muffler (Box 28)
        - Motel-Restaurant Interstate Rte 91 (Box 28)
        - Nashua Corp - Hearing (Box 28)
        - Old Fox Agricultural Sales (Box 28)
        - Edwin Collins/Powder Hill Farm (Box 28)
        - Thompsonville Sewer Dist #2 (Box 28)
        - Phoenix Mutual Life Ins. Co. (Box 28)
        - Rainbows, Inc. (Box 28)
        - Roadway Express, Inc. (Box 28)
        - U.S. Envelop Co. (Box 28)
        - Webbers Truck Service (Box 28)
      - Essex (Box 29)
        - Essex Misc, 3 folders (Box 29)
        - Clairol Corp. (Box 29)
        - CT Water Co. (Box 29)
        - Robert E. Craft, Inc. (Box 29)
        - Essex Auto Salvage, Inc. (Box 29)
        - E. E. Dickinson Co. (Box 29)
        - Griswold Inn (Box 29)
        - L. C. Doane Co. (Box 29)
        - Philips Park, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Pratt Read, Inc. (Box 29)
        - Pratt Read & Co. (Box 29)
        - Steamboat Dock (Box 29)
        - Turbo Products Div., 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Verplex Co. (Box 29)
      - Fairfield (Box 29)
        - Fairfield Misc, 4 folders (Box 29)
        - Town of Fairfield (Box 29)
        - Aristol Co., 3 folders (Box 29)
        - Associated Treatment (Box 29)
        - Bpt Moulded Products (Box 30)
        - Bullard Co., 2 folders (Box 30)
        - Chevron Oil Co. Car Wash (Box 30)
        - Circle Collision Inc. (Box 30)
        - Fairfield Clark Ind. (Box 30)
        - Clark Metal Products (Box 30)
        - CT White Truck Co., 2 folders (Box 30)
        - Continental Motors (Box 30)
        - Soug’s Garage (Box 30)
        - E.I. Dupont DeNemours (Box 30)
        - Dupont Co. (Box 30)
        - Eastern Turnpike Colors (Box 30)
        - ESB Corp.Exide, 3 folders (Box 30)
        - Fairfield Generator Service (Box 30)
        - Fairfield Associated Transport, Inc. (Box 30)
        - General Electric Co. (Box 30)
        - Glove Reconditioners, Inc. (Box 30)
        - Handy & Harmon, 2 folders (Box 30)
        - Harry O’s Inc. (Box 30)
        - Heime Universal, 2 folders (Box 30)
        - C.O. Jelliff Corp., 2 folders (Box 30)
        - J. L. Lucas & Son, Inc. (Box 30)
        - Mike’s Auto & Truck Repair (Box 30)
        - McKeesson (Box 30)
        - Metal Specialties, Inc. (Box 30)
      - Fairfield (Box 31)
        - Parish Court Elderly Housing (Box 31)
        - The Patterson Club, 3 folders (Box 31)
        - Giles T. Phillips & Assoc. (Box 31)
        - Sturm & Ruger & Comp., 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Superior Plating, 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Farmington (Box 31)
        - Farminton Misc., 3 folders (Box 31)
        - Conn. Spring Corp. - Hearing (Box 31)
        - Farmington Subsurface Problems (Box 31)
        - Farmington Siltation & Erosion (Box 31)
        - Bagdigian Subdivision Lot A (Box 31)
        - Calgon (Box 31)
        - Chester Caniewski (Box 31)
        - CT Sand & Stone Corp., 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Corporate Acres (Box 31)
        - Dell Mfg Co., Inc. (Box 31)
        - Edmunds Mfg. Co. (Box 31)
        - Elliot Corp. (Box 31)
        - Farmington Woods (Box 31)
        - Fletcher Terry Co. (Box 31)
        - Frese Imported Auto Works (Box 31)
        - Charles W. House, Inc. (Box 31)
        - Motorlease Corp. (Box 31)
        - Mott Metallurgical Corp. (Box 31)
        - New England Spring (Box 31)
        - New England Aircraft Prod., 2 folders (Box 31)
        - New Haven Trap Rock, 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Pioneer Steel Ball, 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Pioneer-Thomson (Box 31)
        - Pratt & Whitney/Turbo Power & Marine (Box 31)
        - Rider Maintenance Service (Box 32)
        - Rytman Hearing (Box 32)
        - Security Ins. Co. (Box 32)
        - Smith Gates Corp. (Box 32)
        - Stauffer Chemical Corp., 2 folders (Box 32)
        - TAC IV Assoc. - Hearing (Box 32)
        - John E. Toffolon d/b/a Corporate Acres (Box 32)
        - University of CT Health Center (Box 32)
        - James E. Waterman (Box 32)
      - Franklin (Box 32)
        - Franklin Misc (Box 32)
        - Bankroft Mfg. (Box 32)
        - Beckwith Bros. (Box 32)
        - Colchester Egg Farm, 3 folders (Box 32)
        - Richard Crooks (Box 32)
        - Eastern CT Truck Sales, Inc. (Box 32)
        - Franklin Professional (Box 32)
        - Masti-Kure Products, Inc., 2 folders (Box 32)
        - Nathan P. & Nathan R Cushman (Box 32)
        - Outdoor Mart (Box 32)
        - Ralston Purina Co., 2 folders (Box 32)
        - Julius Rytman - Hearing (Box 32)
        - Thames Valley Truck Center (Box 32)
        - Herman Weingart (Box 32)
      - Glastonbury (Box 33)
        - Glastonbury Misc., 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Town of Glastonbury (Box 33)
        - Town of Glastonbury - Hearing, 1976 January (Box 33)
        - Glastonbury Siltation & Erosion (Box 33)
        - Glastonbury Landfill (Box 33)
        - Alco Auto Tech. (Box 33)
        - Arbor Acres, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Asco Auto Body (Box 33)
        - Beckerman (Box 33)
        - Brent Chemicals (Box 33)
        - Joy Brickman (Box 33)
        - CT Galvanizing, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - CT Plating (Box 33)
        - Cycle Worls, Inc. (Box 33)
        - Dick’s Arco Service Sta (Box 33)
        - Dondi Services, Inc., 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Flannagan Brothers, Inc., 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Glastonbury Dyeing & Finishing Co. (Box 33)
        - Hills Country Club (Box 33)
        - Glastonbury Toiletries, Inc. (Box 33)
        - Hallmark Tire Co. (Box 33)
        - Hampden Oil Co. (Box 33)
        - Heritage Auto Body, Inc. (Box 33)
        - J & B Auto Trans, Inc. (Box 33)
        - MacClain Trucking Co. (Box 33)
        - Matson Mill, Inc., 5 folders (Box 33)
        - New England Fotoworks, Inc. (Box 33)
        - Quality Name Plate, Inc., 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Reb Industries/Glastonbury Gage (Box 33)
        - Roberts United, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Roser’s Tannery (Box 33)
        - Somar Mfg. Div. Of Diversa Ind. Inc. (Box 33)
        - Velvet Textile (Box 33)
      - Goshen (Box 34)
        - Goshen Misc (Box 34)
        - Goshen Graymound Pk. (Box 34)
        - Hall Meadow St. Pk. (Box 34)
      - Granby (Box 34)
        - Granby Misc. (Box 34)
        - Canal Heights Subdivision (Box 34)
        - Crane Build & Contract (Box 34)
        - Ray Evansion (Box 34)
        - Charlie Foreman (Box 34)
        - Marko Auto Parts (Box 34)
        - Powers Chevy (Box 34)
        - S & I Associates, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Greenwich (Box 34)
        - Greenwich Misc, 5 folders (Box 34)
        - Town of Greenwich (Box 34)
        - Town of Greenwich Refuse Incinerator (Box 34)
        - Town of Greenwich Oil Spills (Box 34)
        - American Can Co., 3 folders (Box 34)
        - American Felt Co., 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Development on Audubon Pond Milio (Box 35)
        - Avco Corp (Box 35)
        - Avco Corp - Hearing (Box 35)
        - Byram Shore (Box 35)
        - Salvatore Cerrelli (Box 35)
        - John Chila Auto Body Shop (Box 35)
        - Collins Dev. Corp. (Box 35)
        - Combustion Equipment Assoc., Inc. (Box 35)
        - Consolidated Diesel Electric Co., 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Cos Cob Power Station (Box 35)
        - Alice Doll Dutton (Mrs. B.A.) (Box 35)
        - Electrolux, 4 folders (Box 35)
        - Exxon/Humble Oil & Refining (Box 35)
        - Exxon/Byram Terminal (Box 35)
        - Fairview Country Club, 3 folders (Box 35)
        - Frency Automotive (Box 35)
        - Laurelton Convalescent & Nursing Home (Box 36)
        - GAF Corp., 5 folders (Box 36)
        - Gateway Park Assoc (Box 36)
        - Gateway Park Assoc - Hearing (Box 36)
        - Greenwich Catholic Elementary School System, Inc. (Box 36)
        - Greenwich Laurelton Convalescent Home (Box 36)
        - Greenwich Land Development (Box 36)
        - Griffin Ford, Inc. (Box 36)
        - Harbor View Heights (Box 36)
        - George E. Hite, III (Box 36)
        - Estate of Jeremiah Milbank (Box 36)
        - William Rosenwald (Box 36)
        - Clifford Marshall (Box 36)
        - Mediatrics, Inc. Nursing Home (Box 36)
        - Pray Automotive Corp. (Box 36)
        - Round Hill Country Club, Inc., 2 folders (Box 36)
        - Mr. & Mrs. Donald W. Russell (Box 36)
        - John C. Steers (Box 36)
        - Stanley Stevens (Box 36)
        - Frederick M. Supper (Box 36)
        - Tom’s Auto Repair (Box 36)
        - Town & Country Motors (Box 36)
        - Treated Sanitary Discharges (Box 36)
        - Vlado Foreign Car Specialist (Box 36)
        - Wingfield Spa & Racquet Club (Box 36)
        - Greenwich Water Co./Mianus River Filter Plant, 3 folders (Box 36)
        - Katherine D. Wright (Box 36)
      - Griswold (Box 37)
        - Griswold Misc (Box 37)
        - Griswold Town of (Box 37)
        - Griswold Town of Combined Sewers (Box 37)
        - American Sand & Gravel, Inc. (Box 37)
        - Alfred Goldstein (Box 37)
        - Edward Gavelin - Hearing (Box 37)
        - Modern Leather Co. (Box 37)
        - New England Paper Mills, Inc. (Box 37)
        - Pasquale Computaro (Box 37)
        - Plastic Wire and Cable Corp., 2 folders (Box 37)
        - E.I.S. Reports & Data (Box 37)
        - Griswold Mycelium Composting Operation (Box 37)
        - Landsco Compost Area (Box 37)
        - United Merchants (Box 37)
        - Wedgewood Fabric Corp/Griswold Industries (Box 37)
        - Wyre-Wynd, 4 folders (Box 37)
      - Groton (Box 37)
        - Groton Misc., 2 folders (Box 37)
        - Groton Town of (Box 37)
        - City of Groton STP (Box 38)
        - Town of Groton Fieldcrest Estates (Box 38)
        - City of Groton/Dept. Of Utilities (Box 38)
        - Amerada Hess Corp./Hess Oil & Chemical Div. (Box 38)
        - Arwood Corp., 2 folders (Box 38)
        - Auto World Realty (Box 38)
        - Avery Heights Assoc. (Box 38)
        - Avery Heights Assoc. - Hearing (Box 38)
        - Town of Groton/Bel-Aire Sect./Updated facilities plan (Box 38)
        - Branford Court STP (Box 38)
        - Nautilus Park (Box 38)
        - Dolphin Homes, Inc. (Box 38)
        - Foreign Cars, Ltd (Box 38)
        - Full Cycle, Inc. (Kowasaki of Groton) (Box 38)
        - Fusconi Cleaners & Tailors (Box 38)
        - Fusconi Cleaners (Box 38)
        - Electric Boat/General Dynamics, 6 folders (Box 38)
        - Electric Boat/General Dynamics, 6 folders (Box 39)
        - Joseph Lentine Car Wash (Box 39)
        - Groton Medical Park Inc., - Hearing (Box 39)
        - Town of Groton Regional Vocational Tech Schnno (Box 39)
        - Gold Star Motors (Box 39)
        - Hobs Island (Box 39)
        - Hendell’s (Box 39)
        - Mumford Cove (Box 39)
        - Mystic Oral School STP (Box 39)
        - Systic River Homes (Box 39)
        - Nautilus Pk STP (Box 39)
        - Pfizer Inc., 6 folders (Box 39)
        - Patton & Webster/Div of Auto World (Box 39)
        - Pfizer Corp., 3 folders (Box 40)
        - Groton Pumping Station (Box 40)
        - Speedy Muffler King (Box 40)
        - TNM Lathrop, Inc. (Box 40)
        - Univ. Of CT, Marine Lab (Box 40)
        - U.S. Navy (Box 40)
        - U.S. Coast Guard (Box 40)
      - Guilford (Box 40)
        - Guilford Misc (Box 40)
        - Allied Color (Box 40)
        - Andrews, Snowden (Box 40)
        - Frederick Bauer (Box 40)
        - Jacqueline Blaha - Hearing (Box 40)
        - Beauvais Printing Co. (Box 40)
        - Bluff Head (Box 40)
        - Doris Bradshaw (Box 40)
        - John Bunce (Box 40)
        - John Carr (Box 40)
        - CT Water Co., 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Addressograph Multigraph Corp. (Box 40)
        - Guilford Development Projects (Box 40)
        - Charles E. Fiero (Box 40)
        - David Fisher (Box 40)
        - Francis L. Garred (Box 40)
        - George Schmitt & Co., Inc. (Box 40)
        - Robert Gunther (Box 40)
        - Kenyon Marine (Box 40)
        - Marjorie Jenkins (Box 40)
        - Harry Hodge (Box 40)
        - Jimmy’s Auto Wreckers, Inc. (Box 40)
        - Lake Quonnepaug (Box 40)
        - Maple Shade Farm, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - MERZ (Box 41)
        - Thomas Mitchell/Mirto-Dr. Lynch (Box 41)
        - River Colony Sec B (Box 41)
        - Sachems Head Yacht Club, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Barbara Schultz (Box 41)
        - John Salovie (Box 41)
        - John Solovie - Hearing, 1973 October (Box 41)
        - Seaview PRD (Box 41)
        - Paul Seward (Box 41)
        - Shore Line Times Printing Co., Inc., 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Beverly Stabile (Box 41)
        - Charles Stachelbert, Jr. Jean Storms, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Eleanor Walden (Box 41)
        - Waverly Chemical Co., Inc., 5 folders (Box 41)
        - Town of Guilford (Box 41)
        - John H. Wedig (Box 41)
        - Witcomb Motors, Inc. (Box 41)
        - Richard Whitney (Box 41)
        - Marie Young (Box 41)
        - Guilford Misc. (Box 41)
        - Strawberry Hill (Box 41)
        - Fire Assoc. (Box 41)
        - George Theroux (Box 41)
        - Fredeick Ulbrick (Box 41)
        - Walden III, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Haddam (Box 42)
        - Haddam Misc, 2 folders (Box 42)
        - Barbara Monterosso Pinebrook Dinner Theater (Box 42)
        - Harper’s Landing Ferry Restaurant (Box 42)
        - Cargo Developers (Box 42)
        - CT Yankee Plant, 7 folders (Box 42)
        - Frismar, Inc. (Box 42)
        - Haddam Jr./Sr. High School (Box 42)
        - Harpers Landing, Inc. - Hearing (Box 42)
        - Raymond Kavarsky/Kay Bldg & Development Corp. (Box 42)
        - Barbara E. Monterosso - Hearing (Box 42)
        - Barbara E. Monterosso (Box 42)
        - Prestige Homes/Martin Bonacci (Box 42)
        - Sibley, 4 folders (Box 42)
        - Valeriay Veal Farm (Box 42)
        - Hamden Misc, 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Hamden Town of (Box 43)
        - CT Motor Club (Box 43)
        - Detroit Steel Corp. (Box 43)
        - Eaton Woods (Box 43)
        - Freedom Corp/Freedom Honda (Box 43)
        - Foster’s Garage (Box 43)
        - Giering Mfg. (Box 43)
        - Himmel Bros., 2 folders (Box 43)
        - H. A. Leed Co., Inc. (Box 43)
        - High Standard (Box 43)
        - International Business Machines Corp. (Box 43)
        - Lake Whitney Filter Plant (Box 43)
        - Landfill Associates, 3 folders (Box 43)
        - Hamden Tire Salvage (Box 43)
        - Hamden Bldg Salvage (Box 43)
        - LFE Corp/Fluids Control Div. (Box 43)
        - Maaco Auto Painting & Bodyworks (Box 43)
        - New England Coach, Inc. (Box 43)
        - New Haven Water Co. (Box 43)
        - Olin/Pine Swamp (Box 43)
        - Paradise Country Club (Box 43)
        - Hamden Power Equipment & Service Co. (Box 43)
        - Sleeping Giant State Park (Box 43)
        - Porce-Len (Box 43)
        - Angelo Tomasso (Box 43)
        - Tomasso Trap Rock (Box 43)
        - Town Fair Fire Center (Box 43)
        - Troiano Rd./Groundwater Pollution, 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Veggo Larson Co. (Box 43)
        - Whitney Blake Co. (Box 43)
        - Whitney Center (Box 43)
      - Hartford (Box 43)
        - Hartford Misc, 3 folders (Box 43)
        - A-Z Auto Sound System (Box 43)
        - Allied Platers, Inc. (Box 43)
        - Amoco Gas (Tire Center) (Box 43)
        - Arrow Hart, 4 folders (Box 43)
        - Roger J. Au & Sons, 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Whitney’s Alignment & Frame Specialties (Box 44)
        - Whitney Chain, 3 folders (Box 44)
        - Whitney Chain - Hearing (Box 44)
        - Billings Forge (Box 44)
        - Bob’s Exxon Station (Box 44)
        - Capewell Mfg. Co. (Box 44)
        - Career Automotive Center (Box 44)
        - Chase Family partnership (Box 44)
        - City Tire Co., Inc. (Box 44)
        - Brainard Ford Truck Sales (Box 44)
        - Capitol City Engraving (Box 44)
        - Colt Industries (Box 44)
        - Colt Patent Firearms (Box 44)
        - CL&P (Box 44)
        - Cushman Ind., 2 folders (Box 44)
        - CRRA - Mid CT Project (Box 44)
        - D-V Motors (Box 44)
        - Wyllie Dowd & Olson (Box 44)
        - Dresser Industries (Box 44)
        - Equipment Service, Inc. (Box 44)
        - Emhart (Box 44)
        - Hartford Fishkill (Box 44)
        - Friendly Garage & Repair (Box 44)
        - Godells Repair & Body Shop (Box 44)
        - Hales Auto Body (Box 44)
        - Henry Souther Eng. Co. (Box 44)
        - Horace Bushnell Congregate Homes (Box 44)
        - Htfd Dist/U.S. Steel Supply (Box 44)
        - Maverick Corp. (Box 44)
        - Hartford Steam Co. (Box 44)
        - Hartford Cooperage Co. (Box 44)
        - Hartford Tech Institute (Box 44)
        - HELCO/So. Meadow Station (Box 44)
        - Herrings Service Center (Box 44)
        - Heublein, Inc. (Box 44)
        - Holt Assoc. (Box 44)
        - Hartford Indus. Tractor (Box 44)
        - International Auto Radiator (Box 44)
        - Johns Auto Inc. (Box 44)
        - Killian Ball Div./Superior Steel (Box 44)
        - Kelly’s Motors (Box 44)
        - Lance Enterprises, inc. (Box 44)
        - Metropolitan District (Box 44)
        - Merrow Machnie (Box 44)
        - Mitchells Auto Repairs (Box 44)
        - Morin & Sarra Auto & Truck Repairing (Box 44)
        - NBA Auto Service (Box 44)
        - Peabody Testing Corp. (Box 44)
        - Hartford Redevelopment Agency (Box 44)
        - Rayal Welding Co. (Box 44)
        - John Russo Trustee - Hearing (Box 44)
        - Hartford Sewage Station (Box 44)
        - Shepard Park Co. - Hearing (Box 44)
        - Stanley Rockwell Co. (Box 44)
        - St. Francis Hospital (Box 44)
        - Speedy King Muffler (Box 44)
        - Stop & Go Transmission (Box 44)
        - Suissman & Blumenthal, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Superior Tire & Auto Center (Box 45)
        - Technichrome Color Lab - Hearing (Box 45)
        - 3M Business Products Center (Box 45)
        - Superior Ball Co. (Box 45)
        - M. Swift & Sons (Box 45)
        - Technichrome Color Lab (Box 45)
        - Tyrman & Berman Tire Center (Box 45)
        - Underwood Corp. (Box 45)
        - Universal Vacuum Products (Box 45)
        - University of Hartford (Box 45)
        - Veeder Industries, Inc. (Box 45)
        - Warner Murphy (Box 45)
      - Hartland (Box 45)
        - Town of Hartland (Box 45)
        - Hartland Siltation & Erosion (Box 45)
        - Homewood Subdivision (Box 45)
        - Goetz Subdivision (Box 45)
      - Harwinton (Box 45)
        - Harwinton Siltation & Erosion (Box 45)
        - Mitral Corp, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Town of Hawington (Box 45)
        - Harwinton Shopping Center (Box 45)
        - Angelia & Gervasini Bldg Metals Inc., 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Hebron: (Box 45)
        - Hebron Misc., 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Municipal Dump (Box 45)
        - Millstream Rd. Erosion Problem (Box 45)
        - M & M Assoc. (Box 45)
        - Porter Bros. Inc. (Box 45)
        - Nuclear Tech. Corp. - Hearing (Box 45)
        - Nuclear Tech Corp (Box 45)
      - Kent (Box 45)
        - Kent Misc, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Cap Kenico Hearing, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Housatonic Valley Assoc. Inc. (Box 45)
        - Housatonic Enterprises (Box 45)
        - Kent Colonial Campground (Box 45)
        - Kent Mfg. Co. (Box 45)
        - Kent School (Box 45)
        - Lake Wauramaug State Park Campground (Box 45)
      - Killingly (Box 46)
        - Killingly Misc, 2 folders (Box 46)
        - Killingly Sewerline Erosion Problem (Box 46)
        - Killingly Town of - Hearing (Box 46)
        - Acme Cotton Prod. Co., 3 folders (Box 46)
        - Burgenayer Bros., Inc. (Box 46)
        - CEM, 3 folders (Box 46)
        - Delta Rubber Co., 4 folders (Box 46)
        - Frank & Richard DiBonaventura (Box 46)